<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Konjure</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Konjure</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2019 01:53:09 +0330</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>API Reference</title>
      <link>/main/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/main/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Welcome to the official documentation for Konjure – your gateway to streamlined Infrastructure-from-Code transformation! In a world where agility and automation are the cornerstones of modern IT, Konjure stands as your trusted companion for translating code into robust, scalable infrastructure. This documentation is your key to unlocking the full potential of Konjure, where we&amp;rsquo;ll guide you through every facet of this innovative tool.
Whether you&amp;rsquo;re a battle-hardened DevOps engineer or a curious developer venturing into the realm of infrastructure automation, Konjure equips you with the tools to effortlessly craft and manage your environment using code.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started</title>
      <link>/getting-started/main/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2019 01:53:09 +0330</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/getting-started/main/</guid>
      <description>Getting Started Welcome to the Konjure project! Konjure is an open-source command-line interface designed to simplify the process of generating Kubernetes resources&amp;rsquo; YAML files for your applications. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re working with web services, background jobs, or any other kind of application, Konjure helps you streamline the process by analyzing your code repository and generating the necessary Kubernetes resources based on the detected application type and cloud service dependencies.
Installation To get started with Konjure, you need to install it on your system.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How It Works?</title>
      <link>/how-it-works/main/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2019 01:53:09 +0330</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/how-it-works/main/</guid>
      <description>How It Works Konjure simplifies the process of generating Kubernetes resources&amp;rsquo; YAML files by automating the analysis of your codebase and intelligently detecting application types and cloud service dependencies. Here&amp;rsquo;s a step-by-step overview of how Konjure works:
1. Code Analysis When you invoke the konjure generate command, Konjure starts by analyzing the code within your repository. It supports multiple programming languages such as Go and Java, and it examines the structure and content of your code to understand how your application works.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
